<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
	<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
		<MASTER_PAD_VERSION>4.0</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
		<MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>PADGen 4.0.1.41</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
		<MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data format that allows software authors to provide product descriptions and specifications to online sources in a standard way, using a standard XML schema that allows for data reuse and automated parsing.</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
	</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
	<Program_Info>
		<Program_Name>Shanbit</Program_Name>
		<Program_Version>1.0.4</Program_Version>
		<Program_Release_Month>02</Program_Release_Month>
		<Program_Release_Day>12</Program_Release_Day>
		<Program_Release_Year>2026</Program_Release_Year>
		<Program_Cost_Dollars>14.99</Program_Cost_Dollars>
		<Program_Cost_Other_Code>USD</Program_Cost_Other_Code>
		<Program_Cost_Other>14.99</Program_Cost_Other>
		<Program_Type>Commercial</Program_Type>
		<Program_Release_Status>New Release</Program_Release_Status>
		<Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
		<Program_OS_Support>Win10 x64,Win11 x64,WinServer 2016,WinServer 2019,WinServer 2022,WinServer 2025</Program_OS_Support>
		<Program_Language>English,Spanish</Program_Language>
		<Program_Change_Info>First public release on Microsoft Store.</Program_Change_Info>
		<Program_Specific_Category>Security</Program_Specific_Category>
		<Program_Category_Class>Security &amp; Privacy::Password Managers</Program_Category_Class>
		<Program_System_Requirements>Microsoft Store access, Windows 10 or 11</Program_System_Requirements>
		<File_Info>
			<File_Size_Bytes>0</File_Size_Bytes>
			<File_Size_K>0</File_Size_K>
			<File_Size_MB>0</File_Size_MB>
		</File_Info>
		<Expire_Info>
			<Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
		</Expire_Info>
	</Program_Info>
	<Program_Descriptions>
		<English>
			<Keywords>password generator, diceware, csprng, entropy, offline, security, privacy, qr transfer, encryption, pyblosoft</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>Offline CSPRNG and Diceware password generator</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>Shanbit: Secure offline CSPRNG/Diceware generator with real-time  Shannon entropy info.</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>Shanbit is a secure, 100% offline app featuring CSPRNG-based generation and Diceware methods. It includes real-time Shannon mathematical entropy control (security bits) and QR code transfer to avoid clipboard sniffing. Private and local by design.</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>Protect your digital life with robust passwords generated via CSPRNG and Diceware methods. Shanbit works 100% offline and features real-time Shannon entropy control to visualize mathematical strength (security bits). It includes a volatile session history (RAM only) and secure QR transfer to mobile devices, preventing clipboard sniffing. Ideal for developers and privacy-conscious users seeking security without cloud dependency.</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>Shanbit: Offline password and diceware generator with measured Shannon entropy.

Protect your digital life with mathematically robust passwords generated instantly on your own device. Shanbit is the ultimate tool for developers, sysadmins, and privacy-conscious users who need to generate secure credentials without relying on the cloud.

Main Features:
- Standard Cryptographic Generation: Create keys using combinations of uppercase, lowercase, numbers, and symbols. Powered by Cryptographically Secure Pseudo-Random Number Generators (CSPRNG).
- Real-time Shannon Entropy Control: Visualize the actual mathematical strength of your keys (security bits) instantly as you generate them. Aim for +80 bits for maximum security.
- Integrated Diceware Standard: Generate memorable yet unhackable passphrases based on randomized word lists.
- Extreme Local Privacy: Volatile history that stays only in RAM and is destroyed upon closing the session. Your keys never touch the hard drive or the internet.
- Encrypted QR Transfer: Move your keys to your mobile device instantly without using Windows clipboard, avoiding "sniffing" by other local software.
- Dynamic Bilingual Interface (ES/EN): Switch between Spanish and English seamlessly.
- Modern and Fast Interface: Designed for productivity with dark mode and one-click copy.
- Zero Tracking: No ads, no telemetry, and 100% local operation.

Ideal for creating database keys, Wi-Fi access, bank accounts, and API tokens. Take control of your cybersecurity today with Shanbit. Available as a one-time purchase on the Microsoft Store.</Char_Desc_2000>
		</English>
	</Program_Descriptions>
	<Web_Info>
		<Application_URLs>
			<Application_Info_URL>https://apps.microsoft.com/detail/9NR12VDV9NM5</Application_Info_URL>
			<Application_Order_URL>https://apps.microsoft.com/detail/9NR12VDV9NM5</Application_Order_URL>
			<Application_Screenshot_URL>https://i.postimg.cc/65SDMQNj/standard_en.png</Application_Screenshot_URL>
			<Application_Icon_URL>https://i.postimg.cc/mkCtq12j/icon_32.png</Application_Icon_URL>
			<Application_XML_File_URL>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PabloSalinasDev/Shanbit/refs/heads/main/pad.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
		</Application_URLs>
		<Download_URLs>
			<Primary_Download_URL>https://apps.microsoft.com/detail/9NR12VDV9NM5</Primary_Download_URL>
			<Secondary_Download_URL>https://apps.microsoft.com/detail/9NR12VDV9NM5</Secondary_Download_URL>
		</Download_URLs>
	</Web_Info>
	<Company_Info>
		<Company_Name>PyBloSoft</Company_Name>
		<Company_Web_Site_URL>https://apps.microsoft.com/detail/9NR12VDV9NM5</Company_Web_Site_URL>
		<Contact_Info>
			<Author_First_Name>PyBloSoft</Author_First_Name>
			<Author_Last_Name>Developer</Author_Last_Name>
			<Author_Email>support@pyblosoft.com</Author_Email>
		</Contact_Info>
	</Company_Info>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>